# **VISHVA KACHHADIA**

### **Senior Software Engineer**

+91 7048826053

linkedin.com/in/vishva-kachhadia-966777167/

- @ kachhadiavishva@gmail.com
- kachhadiavishva.github.io/portfolio/



### **ABOUT ME**

Passionate Senior Software Engineer with 4+ years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Senior Software Engineer

#### **TatvaSoft**

## 07/2022 - Present ♀ Gujarat, IN

- I Collaborated with product managers to understand requirements and ensure seamless integration of user-facing features.
- Successfully leading and delivering complex PHP projects from conception to completion, meeting or exceeding client expectations.
- Maintained high code quality standards through code reviews, automated testing, and adherence to coding best practices.

#### PHP Developer

#### codExalters Techlabs

iii 10/2019 - 07/2022 ♀ Gujarat, IN

 I have honed my skills in coding, debugging, and optimizing PHP applications to ensure seamless functionality and exceptional user experiences.

### **EDUCATION**

## Computer Engineering (BE)

**Government Engineering College, Rajkot** 

**益** 2016 - 2020

GPA 7.2 / 10

**HSC** 

V.V.S.S, Junagath

**#** 2014 - 2016

**74.8** / 100

### **PROJECTS**

**Title: Projectset** 

Role: Senior software engineer

Software Platforms: Backend (Codelgniter API), Frontend (Jquery, JS, CSS), Database (MySQL).

Title: EGO Delivery Role: PHP Developer

Software Platforms: Backend (Codelgniter API), Frontend (Jquery, JS, Ajax, Bootstrap, CSS), Database (MySQL)

Title: Proportion Fit Role: PHP Developer

Software Platforms: App(Codelgniter API), Database (MySQL), Admin panel (Backend: Codelgniter, Frontend: Jqeury, JS, Bootstrap, CSS)

#### Check out my portfolio to see more work:

https://kachhadiavishva.github.io/portfolio/

### **SKILLS**

PHP	Codeigniter			Re	est Api	GIT
mySQL		url	Ajax		Jquery	7
Javascript		Вос	Bootstrap		HTML/CSS	

### **LANGUAGES**

English		
Hindi		
Gujarati		